- This whole thing is going to
be awesome, awesome, awesome.
I'm telling you,
Operation: Thirty,
Flirty, and Thriving
is going to be one memorable
shindig... I can feel it.
- Yeah, and from
what you told me,
it sounds like it's going to be
way better than the first
time Barry turned 30.
- Oh, yeah, that time Team Flash
spent the whole night
fighting Cicada.
- Well, thanks to
Dr. Orloff's gamma ray,
Barry's got a
second crack at it,
'cause on a cellular
level, he's still just 29.
Hey, what happened?
My readings are
saying that you're...
- Better than ever.
- Okay, so as far as
everything else goes,
I mean, I think we're good.
Chester, you are still in
charge of entertainment.
Allegra, you and I have already
done all the decorating.
Khione is picking
up the cake, so...
- Do you guys think he's
going to be surprised?
- He better be.
- Okay, I just need
to grab my laptop.
Surprise!
- Wally, Dig...
You guys got me.
- Come here, man.
Happy birthday.
- Thanks. Good to see you.
- May your current
rotation around the sun
be your best yet.
- Okay.
Thank you. Guys!
- Yo, party people,
let's get wild!
- It's got dried
sendru and honey.
It'll be good for your
morning sickness, I hope,
and it tastes delicious.
- Okay, cheers.
- Cheers.
- Mmm.
- Oh, yeah?
- Barry, you have to try this.
- Excuse us. Barry,
happy birthday.
Can you settle something for us?
- Sure.
- See, I think I was
a better CCPD captain
because I'm not a meta-human.
- Oh.
- It keeps me objective.
- Chief, having
meta-abilities gives me
a better understanding of
what meta-criminals go through
and how they're thinking.
- Being human
implies I'm treating
meta-criminals and
non-meta-criminals equally.
- Actually, it implies
you're more biased
because non-metas set up the
system in the first place.
What do you think?
- Um, that...
Central City is lucky
to have you both.
- Okay, okay, do you guys
mind if I borrow the man
of the hour for a moment?
I have a special gift for him.
How does it feel being
- Unreal, I guess.
- Because it's special,
Barry, which means it
requires a special gift.
- Dig, I...
- No, no, please, open it.
- We thought we lost it
when Earth-38 was destroyed.
But A.R.G.U.S. Found
it in National City.
It's hard to believe it's
been three years, right?
Sometimes I'll be at
the grocery store, man,
or with my kids, and, uh...
grief will hit me
all over again.
- Yeah.
It's hard.
We don't get the chance
to say goodbye to someone.
- I'm sorry to
hear about Caitlin,
losing her so soon after Frost.
- Eh, having Khione's helped.
But something about it all
still just doesn't feel right.
That's why I-I
can't accept this.
- Barry, Oliver would have
wanted you to have this.
- I'm sorry, Dig.
Maybe we should just
display it in the hall.
- Does Khione need
help with the cake?
- Oh, she said there's a
huge line at the bakery.
So I figured, while
we're waiting,
I might as well give you this.
- You know it's not
my birthday, right?
- It's just a little
something that I made you
for our one-month anniversary.
- It's beautiful.
- And it's not just for show.
I know you've been worried
about the "light meta" buzz,
so I designed this to
conceal your identity.
It's got a facial
transmogrifier inside it.
This way, you can
concentrate on using
all your powers to kick ass
and not on trying
to hide your face.
- Thanks. That'll
come in handy.
- Plus, now got a
little piece of me
keeping you safe out there.
I love it.
And I love you, too.
- ♪ Yo, I'll tell
you what I want ♪
♪ What I really, really want ♪
- ♪ Yo, tell me what you want,
what you really, really want ♪
- ♪ I'll tell you what I want,
what I really, really want ♪
- ♪ Yo, tell me what you want,
what you really, really want ♪
- That's a hit.
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
- ♪ I wanna really, really,
really wanna zigazag, ah ♪
- You know there's a whole party
going on in there, right?
I just needed some air.
- Hmm.
- Hey, thanks for coming
all the way for this.
How are the Himalayas?
- Well, Bakinimal has
been helping me a lot
with my journey to
enlightenment, which is good.
Um, but when Iris told
me about the Red Death,
it kind of gave me an idea.
You know how I can
project my consciousness
into the Speed Force?
Well, I've been doing it to
find alternate timelines.
- What for?
- Since there are
other timelines,
there's probably
another me out there
who has already
achieved enlightenment
and could help me find it, too.
- Wow.
I mean, you already seem
so in touch with yourself.
Can't you do it on your own?
- I wish it was that simple.
Um, true awakening requires a
deep examination of the self.
And when you have baggage
like I do, it's just...
It can hold you back.
- What baggage?
I just... I thought the whole
point of you going to Tibet
was to deal with
things from your past.
- Just forget it.
Happy birthday.
- Sparkling cider
for the hostess.
- Mm.
- Champagne for
the birthday boy.
- Thank you.
- Okay, everybody, ting, ting,
ting, ting, ting, ting, ting.
Please, raise a glass
for the birthday boy.
- Oh.
- Happy birthday.
- Cheers.
- Happy birthday, Barry.
- Speech.
- Speech, speech, speech.
- I mean, what can I
say, except, um, I feel
really lucky to have
the best friends
and family in the world.
So here's to you guys.
I love you all.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Chester, this cider
tastes a little expired.
- It's not just the cider.
- I don't feel so good.
- Yeah, me neither.
- Everybody stop drinking now.
Iris, hey.
- Barry, what is happening?
- Quite the
festivities, Mr. Allen.
My invitation must have
been lost in the mail.
I hope you don't mind
me crashing your party.
- Why all the sour faces?
Don't tell me I've
missed the cake.
- What did you do to them?
- Is this how you
greet an old friend,
especially one that's
just escaped A.R.G.U.S.?
You know, I came right back here
so we could pick up
where we left off.
And now I find out you're
having a party without me.
- Look, I don't know you,
but I know that we can
solve this without violence.
- Mr. West...
I don't want violence.
I simply wish to save the world.
- You don't want to save anyone.
You're a monster who
wants to absorb us all
into your sick mind.
- Is that such an unfair
price to pay for immortality?
- You hurt Iris, I will wipe
every last one of your cells
off this planet.
- Fear not.
Your wife is perfectly
safe and healthy,
and she'll stay
that way forever,
which means your daughter will
never know an orphan's grief.
On the contrary,
little Nora West-Allen
would be the first blood baby
born into a whole new world.
Your anger means nothing, Barry.
Now, last time, I made you
into a blood brother first,
only for your meddlesome
team to rise up against me.
But this time, they
won't have that chance.
And soon, your meager healing
factors will run out, too.
- I don't know
what you're up to,
but you're not going to
get into my head again.
- But, Barry...
I already am.
Time to begin the good work.
Someone didn't drink
their champagne.
- Uh, bro, I'm not
really much of a drinker.
- That's no fun.
Now I'm going to have to
bring the party to you.
- Sweet Duane Jones.
Oh, no, frak this.
- How fascinating.
You're sharing your oxygen
with the embryo inside you.
And she's sharing her
healing factors with you.
- We're going to stop you.
- No, you won't.
I've been playing the
long game, and you...
have already lost.
- Ramsey!
I know you can hear me!
You can't fool me again.
Those visions you
showed me last time,
they were lies,
made to tempt me!
- I never lied to you, Barry.
I just showed you
a future where you
had the power to end death.
But you rejected my offer.
And now your friends
are dropping like flies.
Nash, Caitlin, Frost...
It's quite the list.
- You can't break me again.
- I don't need to, Barry.
This time I have a more
interesting target in mind,
just as fleet-footed,
too, only more perceptive.
- Wally.
Son.
Wally?
Mama needs her medicine.
Wally!
Mama needs her
medicine. Wally...
- I'm sorry, Mr. West.
I thought seeing your childhood
home would be comforting,
but I suppose it
is rather spartan,
especially compared to Barry's.
- Why'd you bring me here?
- Because you need
a friend, Wallace,
and because we can
help each other.
- I'd never help you.
- But you already have.
You see, the last time I
encountered Team Flash,
when I possessed Barry's mind,
I learned what was coming...
A crisis to end the Multiverse.
But I guess it didn't take.
- No, you're wrong.
The Multiverse is dead.
I know because I lost Jesse.
She's never coming back.
- Tell me something, Wallace.
What did you see
out there when you
projected your consciousness...
Alternate timelines...
or other Earths?
Yes, Wallace, you
can sense them.
So isn't it possible that
there's another Jesse Quick
out there somewhere just waiting
for her Prince Charming
to come and find her?
- You're trying to trick me,
but you can't tempt me
with simple desires.
I know my truth.
- And why have you failed in
your quest for enlightenment?
I know you've been wrestling
with the darkness inside you
and how desperate you are
to rid yourself of it.
But you can't, not on your own.
Let me help you.
- How, by turning
me into a zombie?
- No, by unlocking
your true potential.
This is your future,
Wally West.
You will enlighten
the entire world
and all the other worlds
yet to be discovered.
All you have to
do is choose life.
- No, y-you turned everybody
I loved into your slave.
That's not choice.
- I understand your hesitation.
No one has ever really
believed in you, have they?
You have been cut
down your entire life,
forced to watch
your mother suffer.
It is a pain that I
know all too well.
My mother was
diagnosed with HLH,
and I couldn't save
her either, Wally.
I had to watch her die.
- And we have that in common.
- Then you understand what it
is that I'm trying to do...
That it's about more
than just stopping death.
It is about ending the suffering
that we have both endured,
that, together, we can create
a Multiverse where
no one has to watch
their loved ones die...
ever again.
- Okay, okay, just me.
Okay, all your
friends are zombies.
But it's, uh... it's
okay. It's okay.
You just got to call for help.
- Hello? Is anyone there?
- Iris?
Oh, I thought you were a zombie.
- Little Nora's
healing factor...
I-it's holding off
the infection for now.
Look, I locked myself
in a time vault,
but someone cut the power
to the outside comms.
- Iris?
Iris, can you hear me?
- I've been waiting
for you, Chuck.
What, don't you want to
give your lover a kiss?
- No, no, no, no.
You're not Allegra.
You're Ramsey
controlling her body.
- And what a
powerful body it is.
- Doing this to
people ain't a gift.
- What else would you
call eternal life?
- I'd call it hell on Earth.
- You know what?
I'll leave you alone.
Unfortunately, the rest
of my brothers and sisters
have different plans.
- Leave Wally alone.
- Don't worry.
I have no intention
of harming him.
But if I did, it
would be just one more
sacrifice in your name, right?
Sorry.
Is it me, or is the lighting
in here a tad too melodramatic?
Can I get a grip or an
electrician over here?
- What the hell? Where are we?
- Language, Barry,
it's a family show.
Now you'll have to keep up if
we're going to make our day.
After all, you're
the star of the show.
- Wait, what's...
What's happening?
- Okay, ready to try one?
- What is this?
What are you doing?
- Making you look good, champ.
All right, lock it up.
- Hey, man, love your work.
Roll sound.
- Mark.
- Ready, and action.
- Um...
Hi, kids.
I'm the Flash.
Did you know that
when a person survives
an event that others didn't,
it can lead to...
feelings of guilt?
That's a Flash fact.
No, I'm not... I'm
not doing this.
- Cut. That's a cut, everyone.
- Frost.
- It's okay that
she's dead, Barry.
It's more important
that you live.
You're the star, right?
- No. No, that's not true.
- You matter more
than the rest of us.
That's why it's okay
that you got those extra
years and we didn't.
- I didn't want extra time,
not without all of you.
- Oh, that's lunch.
- Wally...
are you okay?
- Young Wallace is
better than ever.
He and I had a very
enlightening conversation.
- Listen to me, Wally.
Whatever Ramsey showed
you, it's not real.
- Shut up, Barry.
Just shut up.
- This anger isn't you.
Ramsey's manipulating you, so
you'll choose to follow him.
It's the only way he can
beat our speed healing
and take over our minds.
- He doesn't care
about you, Wallace.
He's been living with your
father, pawing at your sister,
while you were trapped
in that hellhole.
- You were living my life.
- Wally, I know how hard
it was for you growing up.
- No, you don't! You
don't know anything!
- But Joe and Iris didn't
even know that you existed.
- Keep his name out your mouth.
Joe West is my dad, mine.
He's not yours.
But you stole him
anyway from me.
You got to have two
dads who loved you.
I had nobody, Barry.
You're so selfish.
And you know why?
Because you think that you're
the only person that matters.
- Wally...
Joe loves you.
And I love you.
- Well, I hate you.
- Yes!
- Oh, Barry, Barry, Barry...
what have you done this time?
- No.
No, Ramsey's still
messing with my head.
- Barry, you need to calm down.
- You're not real.
How did I get here?
Wally, he was a blood
brother. He attacked me.
He killed me.
- Dying is the easy part.
Remember?
- It's really you.
- Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Okay, let go.
Barry, let go.
- Wait. If you're here,
that means I'm really...
- You're dead.
Otherwise, why would I
let you hug me that long?
- But if I'm dead, no
one's there to stop them.
Iris, the baby, the... The
whole world is in danger.
- I know.
But it's not just your
world that's in danger.
When I took on the
power of the Spectre,
I thought that I was simply
creating Earth-Prime.
But I was also making
something else...
A new Multiverse to replace
the one that had fallen.
- But when we fought
the Red Death,
she thought she escaped
from her timeline
into an alternate one.
- She is from Earth-4125.
- You're numbering them?
- I've had a bit of
time on my hands...
Keeping an eye on threats
to these new worlds,
like your friend Ramsey Rosso.
He wants to spread
his infectious cells
to every world out there.
- No, I mean, Ramsey's powerful,
but he's not capable
of something like that.
- Right, but with
Wally by his side...
Wally thought that he was
projecting his consciousness
into the Speed Force to
reach alternate timelines,
when, in fact, he was
reaching other Earths.
So, if Ramsey's control
over Wally becomes permanent...
- He'll gain control
over the Multiverse, too.
Now, what have we here?
Ah, a gift from the boy genius.
You were so worried about
Allegra's protection,
you didn't stop and
think about your own.
Don't worry.
In a few moments,
you won't care.
- Sounds like trouble.
- No.
- Khione?
Whoa.
What'd you, uh...
what'd you do to her?
- Same thing I did to
everyone else out there.
I froze all the
water in her body.
Oh, don't worry. She's safe.
- Wait. How did you
know to find me here?
- I was in line
waiting for the cake
when I felt a
presence calling me,
telling me that I
was needed here.
Only, now I get the
feeling the job isn't done.
- This world will be cured soon.
But there are so many
other worlds out there.
I think it's time we started.
- Feel them...
millions of worlds waiting
for your life blood.
- A gateway to the Multiverse.
Thank you, brother.
Now infinite souls will
know my gift and rejoice.
- The attack's starting.
Ramsey's fed his
cells into the breach.
Soon, they are going
to infect your world
and all of the worlds
yet to be born.
- I have to stop him. You
have to get me out of here.
- It's not that simple.
- You have the power of a god.
You can bring me
back from the dead.
- No, I can't...
not while there is a part of you
that doesn't want to go back.
- That's not true.
- You've always been
a terrible liar.
It's...
it's my birthday today.
I didn't want to do anything,
but Iris threw
this party, and...
I-I should have been
grateful, happy.
But all I could
think about was...
Everyone who couldn't be there.
- You've lost a lot
of people this year.
- Yeah, Frost died
fighting Deathstorm.
Caitlin died trying to save her.
I fight some random
mad scientist.
I get three extra years to live.
You know everything
now, right, Oliver?
Tell me, how is it right
I'm alive and they're dead?
How's that fair?
- Life is a lot
of things, Barry.
Fair isn't on the list.
- You don't really believe that.
And if you did, your mom
wouldn't be alive again...
or Tommy or Lance.
You used your powers to bring
back everyone you loved.
- Not everyone.
- Your dad.
- Survive.
- No!
- Ollie, I'm sorry.
- It's... it's okay.
Bringing him back
would have done
too much to alter reality.
And I'd already done enough
to dishonor his sacrifice.
When my father
sacrificed himself,
when he gave me my extra years,
what was I doing with them?
I was wasting them.
I was drowning
myself in this sea
of... of pain and darkness
and saying, Ollie,
if you just...
If you cross one more
name off the list,
if you save your
city one more time,
then you'll absolve yourself
of all of this guilt.
And I was wrong.
This guilt is never
going to go away.
It is something that you
have to learn to live with.
That is why people
sacrificed themselves.
That is why I sacrificed
myself for you,
so that in all of
this darkness...
you...
Could be a guiding light...
A hero.
- Because heroes
don't stop running.
- You're damn right.
So...
are you ready to keep running?
Good.
- Wait, hang on.
You're not going to...
boop me again, are you?
It kind of killed the
Speed Force last time.
- No, no, I'm not gonna...
Not gonna boop you.
- Ow!
That hurts.
- Living hurts.
Add it to the list.
- Wait. You came back, too.
- It's just temporary.
I can only intervene when
the Multiverse is in danger.
- I think you missed me.
- Not as much as I missed this.
Let's go kick some ass.
- Ramsey's cells
are metastasizing
inside that breach.
If we're going to wipe them out,
we need a massive
ultraviolet pulse.
How'd he do that? I thought
you were the Spectre.
- The attack on the Multiverse
is weakening my powers.
I need a clear
shot at the breach.
- The Flash and Green
Arrow together again?
I am honored.
- Don't be.
- Wally, you don't
have to do this.
Too late, Flash.
Wallace worships
a new faith now.
He worships at the
altar of Bloodwork.
- You are starting
to piss me off.
- Why?
I'm only trying to improve your
Multiverse by ending death.
Then I can bring
every world together
under one mind for
singular purpose...
Immortality.
- Those worlds
don't belong to you.
- You're right.
They belong to them.
- Are you, uh... are you
sure this is going to work?
- Trust me.
- That's all I can manage.
- Oh! Aah!
Mm.
What the hell?
Did that come out of me?
Where's Barry?
- He needs your help.
- I'm not going to
fight you, Wally.
Wallace is gone.
- I know you can hear me.
I need you to know I'm sorry,
not just for today,
for all the times I've made you
feel like you didn't matter.
- Everyone has
darkness inside them.
There is no cure for that
pain. We can only accept it.
That's the only
way we can beat it.
You can do this, Wally.
You can beat him.
I know you can!
- No!
- Brother/sister
crime-fighting unit.
No.
No!
- I killed you. I'm sorry.
- I came back.
Now let's go save
the Multiverse.
- Impressive...
but let's see how
you fare against me.
- Oliver.
- I can explain.
- It doesn't matter, man.
- How touching.
Unfortunately, this reunion
will be short-lived.
- That's one ugly
son of a bitch.
- Oliver, we got
you a clear shot.
- Ramsey Rosso!
You have failed this city!
+
- I feel like I just recovered
from the world's worst hangover.
- I think we all did.
- The last thing I remember
is drinking champagne.
What happened?
- Ramsey's having
a very bad day.
- Hey, what about Allegra?
- Chuck.
- What have you done to me?
I'm human again.
- I've cleansed the
entire Multiverse
of your infectious cells.
- including the ones inside you.
- And you killed me.
Now my HLH will return.
- I took care of that, too...
Perks of being the Spectre.
- So it looks like
you'll be spending
the rest of your human
days as a regular criminal.
- Where you're going
to rot until old age,
just like everyone else.
- No.
I was going to cure death.
I was supposed to
save the world.
- Don't worry.
That's our job.
- Thank you so much for
protecting my family.
I don't know how much longer
little Nora and I
could have held out.
- Well, you're welcome.
- I still can't believe
that you're here.
- I'm only allowed to intervene
when the Multiverse
is in danger.
- And now that Barry's
taking Ramsey Rosso
back to A.R.G.U.S.,
it's safe to say
everyone's out of danger.
- So the Multiverse
exists again?
- It's a miracle.
- Uh, isn't it science?
- I think it's a little of both.
- I understand.
It was you.
You're the presence that told me
to go back to S.T.A.R. Labs
so that I could save Diggle.
- Khione, you're connected
to the natural world,
so you were able to use
your powers to expel
the unnatural inside of John.
- That's a lot to digest.
I'm going to go meditate.
- Okay.
So now what?
- Um...
wasn't there a party happening?
- Cheers.
- You okay?
- Honestly, I have no idea.
- Barry told me what
Ramsey showed you...
Your room at Mom's house.
I can't imagine how
painful that was.
- Yeah, well...
I know I'm not going to
find an answer to that pain
in the Multiverse.
I have to look within.
Sometimes it just...
feels impossible.
- To cease from
evil, to do good,
and to purify the
mind yourself...
That is the teaching
of all Buddhas.
What? I read your long-ass
emails you'd send me.
- Thank you. Thanks
for everything.
You're going to be the best mom.
- And you're gonna
be the best uncle.
Mm, come here.
- Guys...
Mmm!
- Lyla wants me back at
A.R.G.U.S. to debrief her
on the festivities.
- Duty calls.
- Hmm.
So...
are you going to get
to see her this time?
- Um...
My...
powers came with rules.
Me and Felicity...
our destiny has been written.
- You sure would be proud of
her, Ollie, the kids, too.
William... he's in college.
Mia...
Mia can climb a salmon ladder,
man, with the best of them.
I know. I know.
I've been keeping
an eye on them...
- Yeah.
- And on you.
John, that cube was
designed to tempt you.
But you did the right thing.
And now all of your brightest
days are ahead of you
because they'll be
spent with your family.
- You're my family, Oliver.
I'm just glad I get to say
goodbye to you this time.
- Me too.
I love you, John.
- Love you, too, brother.
- So you got to tell me
about these other Earths.
I mean, how many other
Flashes are there?
- Uh...
- More than enough, but...
I got to say, nobody is
more impressive than you.
How many times have you
saved your city now... 170?
- 180, actually.
- It's all because of you.
I mean, you started this.
- Well...
- I don't know what my
life would have been like
if I hadn't taken that
train to Star City.
- You still would
have been a hero.
- Maybe.
But you made me a better one.
- You made me a better man.
Prochnost.
- Prochnost.
- Very... very good.
- Okay.
- Okay, Mr. Allen, I think
that I have done enough
to upset the cosmic
order for one night.
Can you get this?
- Are you kidding?
You're a billionaire.
- Well, you...
you can't take it with you.
Oliver.
Yeah.
I mean, you can see
everything, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you think I'm...
I'm doing enough...
with my powers,
with my time here?
- Well, Barry, you tell me.
Do you give people hope?
Are you moving through
your city like a...
guardian angel?
Do you make a difference?
That bolt of
lightning chose you.
Don't ever forget it.
Oh, and...
happy birthday.
- Thanks.