- Mr. Maguire.
At last, we meet.
- Pleasure.
My son was impressed
with your offer.
And given what I'm
looking at, so am I.
- Oh, he's got a
voice for radio, huh?
I'm such a sucker
for an Irish accent,
even on a gangster.
- ♪ Oh ♪
- Ooh. Look, a mystery guest.
- ♪ You're gonna
lose your soul ♪
- All right, Charlie, it's
time to work your magic.
- Please, right this way.
- ♪ You're gonna
lose your soul ♪
- How are we looking?
- Well, it's not the
paperwork that worries me.
What's odd is his willingness
to sell us this warehouse
at a discount, take
crypto over cash.
- Respectfully, only one reason
folks in your line of work
want to buy a warehouse near
the port under the table,
and it's not exactly legal.
- I forgot, how did
you say you and Connor
came to know one another?
- Oh, I didn't.
I'm sorry. I don't
know who she is.
My deal's with your son.
- Mr. Maguire, can we talk?
- What's going on?
- We need to walk.
- Hey, this could be a problem.
She's trying to get him to walk.
The hell do you
think you're going?
- I didn't realize she was
the one calling the shots.
- She's not.
- Could have fooled me.
- Enough.
Let's get on with it.
- I'll need to
confirm the funds.
OK.
Sign the transfer of ownership,
and we are...
- Shh.
Chopper.
We
got to go... now!
Put it back!
- Did you set me up?
Did you set me up?
- FBI! On the ground... now!
On the ground!
That was a lot of mustard
on that sandwich, Pop.
- What?
I've got to commit to sell it.
- Ah, I think you oversold it.
- Here! Let me.
Did you get it?
- Yeah.
Of course I got it.
Mm.
- I'm thinking we keep
these for the honeymoon.
- Oh, Jesus. Unsubscribe.
- Oh, yeah.
- At least he's
in a relationship.
- You know what, Mom?
I am the only reason
you have a grandchild.
- Hey, great timing
on that chopper.
- Yeah, the words
"rooftop" and "sniper"
put a real pep in the
step of the Baltimore PD.
- 621, Pop.
- Right, right.
- 621.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, right. I got it.
I got it. I got it.
- Hey, let's get out of
here before they realize
they were buying a
warehouse we didn't own.
- Look, I get it.
By this point in my life,
I should have two kids
and a husband on
the partner track.
But guess what, Mom.
I'm not you.
She's reminding me of my
geriatric pregnancy years.
Yeah, well, Kevin's
been working late a lot,
so I doubt he'll make it.
But I will ask,
promise.
I'm getting called
into a meeting, Mom.
Got to go. I'll
talk to you later.
- You're welcome.
- What am I thanking you for?
- That signal in the noise
you were looking for?
I think we found it.
I knew it.
- Wherever one of these
distribution hubs pop up,
a spike in fentanyl
overdoses soon follows.
You're looking at the
largest drug trafficking ring
in Europe, hiding in plain sight
behind a series of shills
and numbered corporations.
And if I'm right,
they're about to make
a big push into the U. S.
- So we know the what and
the how, just not the who.
- Not just yet, but now
I know where to look.
Room service!
- Ordered us the good stuff.
Emma!
Hey, wait! You can't
just barge in here!
Emma, what are you doing here?
Emma!
- Oh, my God.
Are you cheating on me?
- Nice.
How long?
Must have been a while.
Stacy seemed pretty torn up.
- Three months.
- Why not just tell me?
- Oh, come on, Em.
Can you honestly say that
you're in love with me?
- I can't believe
we pulled that off.
You were amazing back there.
- We were amazing. Hey,
you ready to celebrate?
Because somebody
might have booked
the penthouse suite
at the Langston.
- By this time tomorrow,
we'll be en route to Italy.
- And then?
- Whatever we want till
the money runs out.
Hey.
You know the best part
about happily ever after?
- I don't know, discovering
that it actually exists?
- Mm.
You don't know what comes next.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey, ditch the truck. I'll
see you back at the bar.
- ♪ Last night,
I was dreaming ♪
- Come on. Come on. Get up.
Let's go.
- You lovebirds decide
on a destination yet?
- Oh, he won't let go of Mexico,
and I won't budge on Spain.
- Why not both, huh?
Repeat after me, son:
marriage is compromise.
- You're telling me.
- Bird!
Come on.
We just pulled off the
biggest job of our lives.
I'm sure you can spare
one second to celebrate.
- Yeah, call me conservative.
I like the small
scores, under the radar.
What we just did
makes me nervous.
- You got to gamble big
if you want to win big.
- I will celebrate once
I transfer the funds
into the offshore
account I set up.
Can you hand me the cold wallet?
- Sure can.
- ♪ Just who was
holding me tight ♪
- What?
No.
No, no,
no, no, no, no.
- You know the best part
about happily ever after?
You don't know what comes next.
- Hey. Call her.
Charlie.
Charlie!
Call her right now!
- Call who?
What's going on?
- The number you've
dialed has been changed,
disconnected, or is
no longer in service.
- Vodka martini,
rocks, extra dirty.
- Decisive. I like it.
- I've had...
- A bit of a day,
so whatever this is, hard pass.
- You want to talk about it?
I'm a very good listener.
- How was Hawaii?
You have fun with the fam?
Sunburn's starting to peel.
Trace of purple nail polish
from your daughter... or son.
I don't want to be gendered.
And then there's this.
Oh, I drink mai tais now.
And honestly, the cliché tan
line from your wedding ring
was all I needed, so...
whatever man-whore business trip
you're hoping to have
here in Charm City,
it won't be with me.
- Cool. Have a good one.
- Hawaii sounds nice.
Resync By M_I_S
www.opensubtitles.org
- Relationships.
What a racket.
- A shell game to conceal
who you really are.
- It's exhausting, isn't it?
Lying to each
other all the time.
- But not just
lying to each other.
I mean... lying to
ourselves, really.
Whew.
So what happened?
- She lied to me
about who she was.
- Mm.
I'd promise not to
do the same, but...
we both know that'd be a lie.
So what do you do?
- Oh, me? I'm a...
I'm a yoga instructor.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- No man bun?
- I got rid of it last year.
It was attracting the
wrong kind of attention.
You?
- Oh, me? I'm a...
pageant queen turned
rocket scientist.
- Mm.
- Turns out, my passion,
it was...
Up there the whole time.
- Well, I bet those
pageants really
prepared you for NASA, though.
- Oh, you have no idea.
The only people more
competitive than beauty queens
are those bitches at NASA.
- ♪ Every kiss, every
hug seems to act ♪
- OK, no.
- ♪ You're getting
to be a habit ♪
- A scented candle
influencer? Impressive.
- Says the girl who grew
up in a... dolphin cult?
- ♪ You're getting
to be a habit ♪
- OK, now tell me something...
true.
- I'm a criminal.
- I'm CIA.
- ♪ For my own ♪
♪ I can't break away ♪
♪ I must have you every day ♪
- ♪ As regularly
as coffee or tea ♪
- It was nice to meet you, Em.
- ♪ You've got me
in your clutches ♪
♪ And I can't get free ♪
♪ You're getting to
be a habit with me ♪
You...
You charged the
drinks to your room.
- Wait.
- What?
- Are you hungry?
- I'm starving.
- This is the most
unstructured burger.
- You got a little
something on your...
It's where?
- Chaser.
- Bottoms up.
Wait. You have to
look me in the eye.
Otherwise, it's seven
years of bad sex.
- Morning.
- I showered.
- OK.
- I reeked of alcohol
and terrible decisions...
Not that you were
a bad decision.
I mean, we didn't even...
- No.
No, we didn't.
- So...
what did you say you do again?
- I'm a classical musician.
- Mm. Piano.
Weirdly, no.
Theremin.
- The theremin?
- The beauty of it is,
it's all electricity.
- Hmm.
- You don't even
need to touch it.
- OK, Beatles or Stones?
- Stones, all day.
- Every day.
- Yeah.
A negroni, really?
What? I'm not a gin person.
- Yeah, you're not a gin person
till you've had the
perfect negroni.
- Ooh.
Barroom brawl?
- No, actually.
Old roommate of mine
tried to steal my apple.
Put a blade in me
before I took it back.
- You almost lost your
life over a piece of fruit?
No, not me.
Him.
You got to take 'em.
- I'm not stealing slippers.
I'm a rule follower.
- See, the idea is
to respect the orange.
You draw the essence out
without the bitterness.
Maybe we just stay
here, do this.
- For how long?
- Indefinitely.
- Fantasy is one thing, Charlie.
Reality is another.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
Heard about Tina.
Sorry.
- Yeah.
- You were always a
bit of a romantic,
even in the seventh grade.
- Look, you said you
got a line on a thing?
'Cause I got to make up
quick for this last one.
- Yeah, we had a client,
some high roller from D. C.
You know the type...
Hired some girls,
lots of drinks, a lot
of big swinging...
- Yup.
- Anyways, there's
this TV preacher,
runs a megachurch in Arlington.
One too many drinks,
makes it rain.
Big stacks. I noticed.
Seemed like the kind of guy
you'd want to know about.
- Yeah, he does.
- Usual deal?
- I make money, you make money.
- Hey, Charl.
- Yeah.
- If someone's got to
level the playing field
for the rest of us,
I'm glad it's you.
- ♪ I feel it coming ♪
- Come on, dude. You
got to get over it.
She was a total narcissist.
- ♪ I feel it coming ♪
- ♪ Whoa, it's coming ♪
- Hey, Pete, you got to go.
Family stuff.
Yeah, Mickey.
Out of here.
Hey, Dad?
Upstairs. Homework.
- ♪ Whoa, it's
got a hold on me ♪
- 36 hours total AWOL.
I was starting to
think your fake fiancée
was your real fiancée
and the two of you
planned this thing together.
- OK, Birdie.
- No, Mom, really not OK.
I never wanted to
do a job this big.
And now, thanks to Romeo's
romantic blind spot,
not only are we out 10 million.
We are flat broke.
- All right. All right, enough.
What happened happened.
We'll get through it.
We always do.
- Yeah, Pop, forgive
me if I'm not really
in a "let's get the gang
back together" mood.
- ♪ I feel it coming ♪
- Yeah, OK. I got it.
Hey, baby.
I'm glad you're home.
I'm
sorry, Pop. I am.
I'll fix this.
I already got
something lined up.
- Don't worry about
that right now, kiddo.
You just took a dagger
through the heart.
Give it a minute.
- Do we have a minute to give?
- What do you mean?
621.
Code on the Pelican case?
It's Ollie's birthday.
Same code we've been using
since the day she was born.
- Your mother tell you?
- Nah, she didn't need to.
- Don't worry about it.
It's early stage,
memory loss. That's it.
- Pop.
- We're not...
doing this.
So...
this score,
tell me what you're
thinking about.
- How do you feel about
taking from the hand of God?
- Oh.
- This is our target:
Evan Earle III,
aka Pastor Earle.
- We cannot be late to church.
- He's the lead pastor and CEO
of ILLUMIN-8 Fellowship.
This guy, he is no angel.
Let's see what he's
hiding in that church.
- ♪ I've been
holdin' out so long ♪
♪ I've been
sleepin' all alone ♪
♪ Lord, I miss you ♪
- Look at the interior.
It's so much
prettier than on TV.
Don't you think so, honey?
- Oh, I do.
- I mean, really.
- Oh!
- Oh.
- Are you OK, ma'am?
- Yes, thank you.
- I told her she's too old
for four-inch heels,
but you know how it is.
- Closer to God,
that's what I say.
- Amen.
- The devil is hiding,
waiting to prey upon
lambs of our flock.
- Pastor Earle is a
master marketer...
I mean, publishing,
media network, merch.
- Oh, they have
your favorite place.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- You know how I
love the gift shops.
- Yeah, I know.
- ♪ Lord,
I miss you, child ♪
- Hey, Bird, you in yet?
Birdie. Bird.
- Keep your panties
on. I'm coming.
- Despair not,
for through our...
- ♪ Hey, what's
the matter, man ♪
♪ We're gonna come
around at 12:00 ♪
♪ With some Puerto Rican
girls that's just ♪
♪ Dying to meet you ♪
♪ We're gonna bring
a case of wine ♪
♪ Hey, let's go mess and
fool around, you know ♪
- Charlie, you getting this?
- There is not...
- Charlie?
- A more human...
- Yup, I'm on it.
- Than breathing.
- Attendance the last
few years has been flat,
but yet ILLUMIN-8's
profits are decidedly up.
- Breathe deeply.
- Average donation is 10 bucks.
- And give deeply.
- These guys
shouldn't be taking in
more than 35K a sermon.
- You see?
This is why I'm a
lapsed Catholic.
- So obviously they're
laundering money.
Where from?
- Don't know.
- His teeth are whiter
than a Wilco concert.
- You loved that concert.
- With money in your pocket.
- OK.
What's the play?
- The space between his public
persona and private life.
Every Wednesday,
he gets a package.
New week, new burner.
He tosses the old phone,
activates the new one.
We get our hands
on that new phone,
we got the keys to the kingdom.
He stole my purse!
That SOB stole my purse!
Oh.
- Oh, my God.
- You saved her.
- Oh, my gosh. Are you OK?
- Thank you.
Why, thank... oh!
Are you that pastor from TV?
- Are you OK?
- Easy, Karen.
Not everything's a viral moment.
- Who asked you? Mind
your own business.
- Oh, that's the pot
calling the kettle black.
- Pastor.
- That's racist.
- That's not racist!
- You're a proper
hero is what you are.
- I have rights.
- Peace be with you.
- I can film anything I want to.
- Did someone drop a phone?
- Oh.
That's...
Bless you.
Thank you.
- Find anything?
- I did.
Whoever the pastor is
laundering money for,
he's meeting tonight
at some D. C. gala.
If these guys are taking
the risk to meet in person,
they're either celebrating,
or they're scared.
Either way, we can use that.
- Hey, you, like, cranked my
wrist on that purse snatch.
- Ferraris don't wait in line.
Invitation?
So the dirty cash goes in.
The church cleans it.
Then the pastor takes his
cut and donates the rest
around town to buy
access and influence
for whoever it is he's
taking orders from.
- One big D. C. shell game.
And they think we're the crooks.
- Huh.
- Hi.
- So even you can understand it.
I gave him the invitation.
He took my car.
- All right.
I'm on the pastor.
You find his contact.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it also helps
that he's my father.
- So, Emma, your father's
the former governor.
Your brother's a senator.
What does that make you?
- A crushing disappointment.
Oh!
- No, I'm actually
a data analyst
for a logistics firm.
- Oh, that's great.
- A negroni.
Really?
How is it?
- Imperfect.
- Mm.
- No fire trick.
You're here.
- I'm here.
- Let me guess.
They needed a theremin
player for the band.
No.
Actually wanted some face
time with my congressman.
This pothole can't
seem to get fixed.
It's strange, seeing you in
something other than a robe.
- Was that a compliment?
- I can do better.
- You are an old sandbagger,
because I know what you're up...
- We'll see you inside.
May I pray with you, Pastor?
- Of course.
- Break time.
- What do you mean?
- What do you think I mean?
- So your family's...
impressive.
- Mm, only from the
outside looking in.
Spin over substance,
all day, every day.
- Mm.
I own a bar... with my
family in Baltimore.
Who I am is so wrapped up
in who they are that it's...
hard to see past it
sometimes, you know?
- I have the opposite problem.
Been defining myself
against them my entire life.
- Sounds lonely.
- It can be.
Sorry. I got to...
- Yeah.
- Be right back.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
- Hey.
What in the hell are you doing?
- Just blending in.
- Please.
I am the one person who always
knows when you're lying.
- What's going on
with the pastor?
- Well, I identified his
contact, and you're right.
He's nervous, which means
that something's up,
which you would know if you
weren't otherwise distracted.
Charlie, this was your plan.
You brought me on board.
I am here.
Where are you?
Don't do this to me again.
- Hey, sorry about that.
I have to go.
Work thing.
But tomorrow night,
French-fusion place on Concord,
a harpist playing a song
neither of us knows.
- Sounds wonderful.
But...
I have a thing.
You have a thing?
What's going on? Did
something happen?
- It's like you said, Emma.
There's a big difference
between fantasy and reality.
- Can you honestly say
you didn't think about me,
that you don't think
there's something here?
- I didn't.
And I don't.
- Stop.
Did anyone follow you?
- No.
- Leave the suitcase.
We'll take it from here.
Our friend will be in
touch when he knows more.
Get going.
- Thank you.
- Don't let Tina
near that suitcase.
Hey, you know what?
- Too soon.
- Wow.
Look at you.
- I was at a thing.
Talk to me.
- That signal in
the noise you found?
The deputy director ran it
past our friends at the FBI,
and guess what.
- We got a hit?
- Patrick Maguire.
This dude's basically the
Jeff Bezos of fentanyl.
His operations have
doubled in size
in the last three years.
Been on the FBI's
radar for a while,
but they couldn't nail him.
So we traced the
movements of his crew,
hacked into a nearby security
camera, and got this.
- Who's that?
- No clue.
But he stiffed the
syndicate on a deal, so...
Maguire's still here
trying to secure
an East Coast distribution hub.
- Call our friends at the FBI.
I want to be there when
this guy goes down.
- Done and done.
- ♪ You got it ♪
- You guys should have seen
the look on the pastor's face.
I thought he was gonna
crap his holy trousers.
- Beautiful work, guys.
Just beautiful work.
- Except for the part
where Charlie almost blew
the whole operation on
account of some girl.
- ♪ I said ow ♪
♪ Ow, ow ♪
- We'll have to be
smart about this,
launder a little at a
time through the bar.
At least you and Dad can
still start your retirement.
- Yeah, for what it's
worth, I vote Mexico.
Spain's too far away.
- So... there's a
new girl, Charlie?
- Was, not is.
- Why was?
- 'Cause, Mom, like, this is
what I'm good at, all right?
Just this.
- ♪ Do the Everything ♪
- We're not OK with this.
- With what?
- With your mother and I
sailing off into the sunset
while you stay here to fall
on your sword for this family.
You did that once.
- Dad, it's fine.
- Just stop!
It's our fault that
you went inside,
had to survive that hell.
We're in this spot today
because of our choices,
not yours.
- And you're right, Charlie.
You are the best.
The best.
But this can't be
your whole world.
- I got a lifetime of regrets,
and soon I may not
remember any of them.
So no, Charlie, no.
No, we're not walking away
and leaving you holding the bag.
Either we're all
out, or we're all in.
- Mr. Maguire, we're
all set and ready to go.
All right.
- I told you that
deal was rotten.
Should have listened to me.
Stop thinking you're
smarter than me.
It won't end well.
- I'll be right behind you.
- We got movement.
On my count.
- Hold up.
We need to wait until his
whole crew is on the plane.
- You did your job.
Now let us do ours.
- Drop the bag!
Drop the bag!
Get on the ground!
Damn it.
- You good?
How's your wrist?
- It's fine. I'm fine.
Did you get an ID on
our mystery woman?
- Yes. Daphne Finch.
Grew up in Philadelphia
to a single mother,
law degree at Penn,
MBA at Columbia.
Maguire brought her
in a couple years ago
as a kind of consultant.
- The crime
syndicate's consultant?
- Weird, right?
Nothing about this girl
screams Irish gangster.
- It's her.
She's the reason their
operation expanded so quickly.
She's the brains behind
Maguire's syndicate,
which means arresting
Maguire changes nothing.
Pull all available data:
phone records, emails, texts,
and every known associate.
- So we won the battle?
- Yeah...
but not the war.
I got to call you back.
- What happened? Are you...
- I'm fine.
What are you doing here?
- Look, about last
night, I want to explain.
- It's really not necessary.
- No, it is. Look.
My life,
my family, it's...
It's complicated.
The more you know about me,
the faster you'll want to run.
I get it.
We spent 36 hours
in a hotel room.
We barely know each other.
Let's just leave it at that.
- You're wrong.
I do know you.
Coffee, black.
Stones over the Beatles,
all day, every day.
You read people better
than they read themselves.
You're loyal,
but you don't trust easily
or often.
And you're funny,
even though you use it
to protect yourself.
I know you want
something different.
So do I.
I want to take you on that date.
What do you say?
- I say you're right.
I don't trust easily or
often, but last night...
- Last night, I lied
when I said that...
there wasn't
something between us,
when I said I didn't
think about you.
Truth is, I never stopped
thinking about you,
not once, not for a minute.
I...
Emma.
- Maybe we just stay here,
do this.
- For how long?
- Indefinitely.
- Yeah.
Hey, Bird.
Forget everything I
said last night, OK?
We're not gonna chip
away at the debt.
That's not how
this is gonna work.
One last big score gets
us all out for good.
- Yeah, I've heard that before.
- Hey, it's different this time.
- OK.
- Charlie.
- Oh, great.
Looks like we got the
whole family here.
- Ollie?
- Wait, no, hold on, Bird.
Wait. Just wait.
- You won.
Smart kid.
Wonder where she gets it.
This is a nice place, Charlie.
- Look, about your money...
- It's gone. I heard.
Love can be a real bitch, huh?
- You owe us the 10
million you stole
plus an additional 5.
Let's call it the cost
of getting Mr. Maguire
out of prison.
- Why?
I mean, it looks like
you got what you wanted.
You're in charge.
I'm glad I could help
you out with that.
- Careful, Charlie.
There is no angle out of this
except for you doing
exactly what I tell you to.
- OK.
So what guarantee do I have
that you're not just gonna
take your money,
then... take care of us?
- That's the problem
with lying for a living.
You never really know who
you can trust, do you?
- Look, that kind of money,
it's gonna take me some time.
- Which I don't have.
So I suggest you do
what you do best.
Get to stealing, Charlie,
because you are
not gonna be able