Previously on
"The Company You Keep"...
- Simon?
- Yeah, he started calling
last week.
I don't know why.
I don't need to know why.
You can decline.
Claire Fox? Her support
is not the kind you want.
It's amazing
what aligning yourself
with the right people
can accomplish.
Always comes at a cost.
I wanted to introduce you
to Jennifer West.
I think she'd make a great
addition to your campaign.
Connor Maguire is stateside?
What are you doing here?
The feds are
already watching us.
Your father trusts me
to handle things.
You know when I found out
that Daphne was working with
the man who ripped me off...
kick in the balls
that felt like, you know?
That's Daphne's secret
revenue stream.
That covers the deal
Daphne and I had.
- Charlie.
- Yeah.
I finally figured it out.
Figured what out?
17 across. Riposte.
Huh.
Guessing the fencing lessons
I took as a kid paid off.
Thank you.
Do not tell my mom.
Nice.
- What else you got?
- Uh...
mm.
Five down,
Seven letters.
- Hey.
- Huh?
- You good?
- Yeah.
I'm just thinking about
your, uh, crossword.
You know you can tell me
if something's going on.
Hey...
what if we skip work today?
Crawl back into bed,
cue up a film,
pretend the world doesn't exist.
Hmm.
Hello, world.
- I'll be right back.
- Yeah.
Hey.
I knew we'd get something
on the security cams.
Can you make out
our mystery man?
Partial plate?
I'll take it.
No, that's great, Mason.
Yeah, okay I'll see you soon.
You got to go.
As much as I want to stay.
Um, I got a bunch of stuff
to do here anyway, so...
Hey, look, I'm around later
if you want to talk.
Okay, great.
- Okay. Have a good day.
- You too.
- Hey, uh, "Charade."
- Huh?
Five down.
"Charade." It's one of
my parents' favorite movies.
When this thing wraps up,
maybe we can stay in,
watch a little "Charade,"
see where the day takes us.
Yeah, I'd like that.
- Me too.
- I'll see you.
Bye.
What happened to your
associate was regretful,
but I assure you,
Connor Maguire will have...
Don't you mean your brother?
Connor Maguire
will have no impact
on our partnership
moving forward.
I understand we don't get
to choose our family,
but it's not just your brother
that concerns me.
Since we began selling
your product,
the feds have been all over us.
Your partnership comes with
too much heat.
What if I could
turn down the heat?
Say I find a way to get
our product out of
those shipping containers
and back on the streets.
You do that, I think we can find
some way to work
out our differences.
Still we're talking
Coast Guard, port authority,
customs... so, unless you have
friends in high places...
As a matter of fact, I do.
- There she is.
- Hey, babe.
- Oh, that dress is stunning.
- Thank you.
Thanks for meeting me
on such short notice.
Stop. I've been wanting
to catch up.
I hear you've been
spending time in Europe.
- Ooh, la, la.
- I've been consulting
for this big transnational organization,
but I must say
the experience has been
tragically lacking in fine wine
and Italian villas.
Couldn't be worse
than the swamp.
Well, let's just say it is
no toga party at Sigma Chi.
Right?
Well, nothing is.
- Excuse me.
- Yup.
- Mimosas?
- Please.
- Let's make them bottomless.
- All right.
I'm never gonna let you
live that down.
- Okay, can I be real?
- When are you not?
Fair.
The red tape in this town
is killing me.
- Don't get me started.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
If anyone could help me
grease the wheels in Washington
it is the best damn social
chair Kappa Theta ever had.
- I really was.
- I still can't believe
you're chief of staff
to the House Majority Whip.
I thought you'd be working for
the president by now.
Trust me, I'm on it.
I bet you are.
So for your bureaucratic nightmare,
you can always hire lobbyists.
That takes time.
Which I don't have.
Come on.
Give me the good stuff.
Sister to sister.
♪ Over and over again ♪
Well...
if you really want to
cut through red tape,
I may have a guy.
Go on.
His name is John Baylor.
Former MI-6
turned Beltway fixer.
Think of him as a sort of
unofficial lobbyist
who can apply pressure
to the right people.
Your infrastructure,
my contacts.
A rising tide raises all ships.
Isn't that what they say?
Look, I get it.
You respond to strength,
and so do I.
So let me show you what
having your back looks like.
Baylor's a bit eccentric,
but effective.
Just call this number,
and you should know...
hiring him can come at a cost.
Believe me, I can afford it.
I'm not talking money.
In DC, secrets
are currency, babe.
He's got dirt on everyone who
gets into business with him.
Rumor has it he has
a kind of black book,
but this one's full
of blackmail.
You don't say.
That's the car.
The guy I saw right after
the money drop.
Well unfortunately,
this is the only security cam
in the area.
Hopefully one of these images
can give us a full plate.
Once we ID Daphne's
new revenue stream,
we can finally get inside
her operation.
And find out why she's still
slumming it in Baltimore
while Connor's sipping
margaritas in Mexico.
That car's gotta
still be out there.
We just need a better angle.
What about that one?
Are you about to ask me
what I think you about to ask?
Mason, enhance.
There it is. Dodge Charger,
Maryland plate.
Foxtrot, echo, 9, 4, 9, 2, November.
Reported stolen a few weeks ago.
Okay.
Okay, so he used it for the job,
ditched it after the drop.
Pull up all body shops and
salvage yards within
a 50-mile radius.
He can't hide forever.
Charlie.
Otto, hey. Did you chop that
car from the last job yet?
The Charger? Still here.
Why, you wanna take it
for another spin?
No. Look,
scratch chopping it, okay?
I need you to crush it.
Bro, that's cutting into
my bottom line.
I can't sell car parts
if the car's crushed.
No, no, no. Stop, stop.
I need you to hear me
on this, okay?
It's gotta disappear.
You got it?
You're killing me, man,
but fine.
I'll make it up to you.
Yup.
Is that about the car?
Why are you so worried
all of a sudden?
Just being careful.
Hey, uh, do me a favor.
Tell mom to keep Ollie
at Uncle Gio's another
couple days.
I just... I want the dust
to settle on this last job.
Sure.
Um...
yeah, speaking of, uh,
our least favorite regular
just walked in.
Please, sir,
can I have some more?
Sorry, you want us to con a spy?
Ex-spy.
He's got a little black book
that could prove useful to me.
You know what, lady?
I'm getting a little tired
of you and your demands.
Our debt is paid to you.
- Easy, Pop.
- Wrong.
Because now, thanks to you,
Connor and I are in a footrace
to control this organization.
And now, he's in Mexico with
a $10 million head start.
- Thanks to us?
- Don't play innocent with me.
I know you brought him in
to undermine me.
Family drama's
really not our problem.
Yes, it is, because
Connor wants you dead.
Your family too.
And I'm the only one standing
in the way of that happening.
Okay, so...
we steal a little black book.
Lay it on us.
It belongs to a fixer
named John Baylor.
The guy is hired by politicians
to clean up their messes,
ruin their enemies,
pay off whistle-blowers.
- You want his blackmail.
- Now you're catching on.
I like not being dead.
What's the real value
in this for you? Hmm?
I mean, you deal with
criminals, not politicians.
Is there a difference?
Look, if you're, um,
worried about
your little moral code,
no one is in it
who isn't already dirty.
That's how you reach Baylor.
You want us to go after
a real-life James Bond
with nothing to go on
but a phone number.
He's a paranoid,
Cold War relic
with no connection to the world.
It's fun, right?
See? I knew you'd like
a challenge.
Good luck, Nicolettis.
You're gonna need it.
All right, John Baylor,
former agent for MI6, allegedly.
In the late aughts, he was
undercover as a professor
at Thornton College
until the dean blew his cover.
MI6 disavows him,
sends out a burn notice,
revokes his passport,
whole nine.
Wait, wait, hold on a second.
That's all we got?
Guess I didn't need
to bring out the board.
Guy's trained to be invisible.
He knows how to cover
his tracks.
And now, he's using those skills
to profit off of DC's dirtiest.
It's always nice to see
someone land on their feet.
Hey, Pop, did you get
anything on the ground
that would lead us back
to this guy's black book?
Turns out that spying on a spy
is as difficult as you'd expect.
I mean, this guy's
tradecraft is top notch.
He meets his clients
in public places
where it's either
too loud to listen
or too empty
to get close to him.
He uses surveillance detection
routes to run his errands.
Okay, so the usual tricks
aren't gonna work.
We're just gonna have to
lure him to us.
Ooh, you mean hire him.
Buddy of mine at the Drakefield
said that one Ray Tipton Jr.'s
checking out tomorrow morning.
- RTJ?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, he's a worse human than
his dad was a vice-president.
It's all over the tabloids.
What? You never stood in line
at the grocery store?
Well, hey, look, I'm thinking
that RTJ had a wild night
that he's gonna want buried.
So we slip Baylor a phone
with some delicious blackmail.
Give him some more dirt
for his collection.
Along with some malware
that would give me access
to his computer
and all his files.
And then his secrets
become our secrets.
That's good.
Can't hire a fixer without
breaking something.
Oh, I've always wanted
to do this.
Batter up!
- Explain that to me!
- No, don't blame this on me.
Hurry, before anyone hears.
I didn't see your name
on the partner rolls
at Skadden or Latham.
I've got my own shingle.
Do you have the money?
I am so sick
of you bringing us down.
You just barge right in.
Oh, yeah? Maybe if Ray
wasn't such a lying piece...
You just talking, talking,
but you never say anything.
You're talking at me.
Don't talk to me.
Who the hell are you?
Excuse me. Hello?
I said who the hell are you?
Oh, let me guess, Ray sent
another man to manipulate me.
Oh, it's like I said.
It's just like I said, man.
- She's gonna be a problem.
- I'm the problem?
She's gonna sing like a canary.
Canary?
What are you, an ornithologist
- all of a sudden?
- You know, you're a walking
contact high.
- You, shut up.
- I...
Shut up.
Why don't you all shut up?
What are we dealing with?
Things got a little messy
for my client last night.
I need you to make it go away.
Make it go away?
I came here to be with
my boyfriend, and he left
this morning with some hooker.
Takes one to know one, huh?
Look, she's got photos.
I need you to keep her
from leaking anything
to the tabloids.
You, clean that up and
whatever else you've snorted.
You, replace the sheets.
- You.
- Seriously?
I mean, we hired you.
Now, I am literally cleaning
up that cheater's mess.
Don't make me ask again.
So we're looking good.
Poll numbers are up.
Money's coming in.
But this line's heading
in the wrong direction.
Oh, that's David's approval
with the 18 to 29s.
Now, we tried to engage,
but it's hard to get Gen Z to
care about the real issues.
Yeah, maybe with that attitude.
Thank you, Ms. West,
but that's not...
Let's hear what she has to say.
Well, I couldn't help but
notice that you don't have
a dedicated
social media strategist,
and your Twitter feed
shows how well that's going.
Platitudes and infographics?
Blah.
Social media
isn't just about communication.
It's about connection.
For example, Doug, right now
I just know you as
David's campaign manager,
but when I saw that you spent
last Friday night front row
at the Bad Bunny concert,
well, now we're connecting
as people.
So what do you suggest
we do next?
TikTok, Instagram.
You're a charming guy.
Let's use that.
David's a politician,
not an influencer.
I'd argue
they're one in the same.
She's not wrong.
Uh, would you give us a moment?
Where'd this new aide come from?
Don't tell me Claire Fox
introduced her to you.
Yeah, well, Claire helps
shore up political support
from some of our donors,
and I...
Did her a favor.
I really wish you'd told me.
It's not a big deal, Dad. Really.
Plus, Jen has some good ideas.
Just don't assume
she's working for you.
When it comes to Claire Fox,
there's always another agenda.
Oh, I not gonna let you
sweep this under the rug.
I am gonna take these pictures
straight to TMZ.
Come on. Is that necessary?
Treat Ray Ray with
the respect he treated me.
If you do that, the only person
that will get hurt is you.
It doesn't matter what he did.
The woman pays the price. Always.
Which is why you're gonna
take this money.
And you're gonna
forget everything
that's happened here today.
Uh, I gotta...
I gotta take this.
I'm gonna take... I'm gonna
take this, yeah.
- Hey, what's up?
- You were right.
Some government suits
are here asking questions.
Well, you already took care
of that thing, right?
I was getting to it, bro.
I'm slammed.
Where is it now?
The car is on the north side
of the yard.
I'll give them the grand tour.
That should buy you enough
time to do what you gotta do.
Okay, yeah.
I'll be right there.
Hey, uh, so... ha.
I've got a friend
who has a car emergency.
- Uh, I gotta go now.
- Wait.
Do you idiots ever have a day
without a crisis? Huh?
Cut him loose.
We don't need him here anyway.
Good riddance, Dick.
Go.
Now, hand the man your phone
so we can all move on
with our lives.
Thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's with the photos?
Insurance. You don't pay
the rest of my fee
or you decide to disclose
my involvement here,
these go public.
Oh.
What are you doing?
That's the only proof I have
or RTJ and his whore.
Hey, wait.
You can't have digital
evidence floating around.
You never know
who can get to it.
Uh...
Well, I wish I could say
it's been a pleasure.
But it never is.
Wait.
You need to give me a ride.
I would call one,
but you just nuked my phone.
Or I could catch a ride with
one of the paparazzi downstairs.
I thought you had this
all sewn up.
Fine. Come with me.
Can we take a look over here?
That's where I park my junkers.
It wouldn't be down there.
Yeah, I'd still like
to take a look.
Oh.
It's Charlie.
Mm, I'll call him back.
No, go ahead and take it.
These cars aren't going anywhere.
True.
- Hey, you.
- Hey.
I know you're at work,
I'm sorry.
I just, uh...
I wanted to hear your voice.
What's going on?
Stuff with the bar?
Yeah, yeah, something like that.
Hey, I was thinking...
what about a little stay-cation?
Tonight, escape for a few hours
just you and me.
- Yeah, that sounds great.
- Great.
Meet me at the Langston
at 8:00.
Yeah, okay. I'll be there.
It's a date. See you soon.
What do you think?
Looks familiar.
I wasn't using him, you know?
I mean, the parties were fun.
The lifestyle.
I didn't come from much, but...
I really thought
we had something.
And now,
I just feel like a fool.
You were right, what you said.
That the woman
always pays the price.
A word of advice.
It may be hard, but let
the past stay the past.
Bet you see a lotta people
with regrets
in your line of work.
Hey, what are you gonna do
with those photographs?
I'm asking 'cause I got a kid,
and I really don't...
I don't know who you are
or what you're angling for,
but your sob story needs work.
Get out.
Don't ever call me again,
and remember,
I have more on you
than you have on me.
And you just slide
the pancake onto the plate.
And boom.
You're done.
My dad always called this
the dinner of champions.
Sorry, that was lame.
Can we go again?
It was great.
The whole point is connecting
over the little things.
Hey, you wanna try some?
I can't let good kimchi-jeon
go to waste.
Go for it.
Just like that.
Yup. Perfect.
Ah!
Okay.
And dip.
Mm, mm.
It's hot.
Hope I didn't, uh,
step on any toes
with your team before.
I know they only think
I'm here as a favor.
Hey, I chose to hire you.
I just have a hard time believing
people really want me
at the table.
The truth is,
I got most of my jobs
from my parents
calling in favors.
Listen, I still doubt
I'm here because I earned it.
And sometimes I think
even my own team
doesn't see me for who I am
or what I've done.
My parents could've got me
on any campaign,
and I chose yours
because of who you are.
Because I believe in you.
Maybe it's time the rest of
the team sees the real you.
I certainly like him.
No, Pop, what I said is
for like ten seconds,
I thought he made me.
You shouldn't have improvised.
- We had a plan.
- Didn't work, right?
We had one shot with Baylor.
I took it.
- But that's how you get hurt.
- Hey.
- How'd it go?
- Oh, it's fine.
It's gonna be fine.
I swapped the plate,
and then I called your boy
over at Customs Office
to make sure the new plate
pings far, far from Baltimore.
Good. That should keep
the feds off our asses.
Hey, how'd it go with Baylor?
He take the bait?
Um, so he nuked the phone
before we got out of the room,
but I was able to talk
my way into his car.
- He almost made her.
- No, he didn't.
- It was fine. I'm fine.
- He almost made her.
I shouldn't have left.
No, I could've handled that.
Hey, I handled it,
and I got something.
Whoo! Yay, Bird.
Okay, so he had this key.
Make was Belson.
Printed on it was RMO32.
So I gave it to my guy Stosh
to see what businesses
in the area use that brand
and that locker model.
Because before
he nuked the phone,
he took all of these
photos of the blackmail
with this old-school spy camera.
- The guy's a total Luddite.
- So wait a minute.
So you're thinking that
Baylor's black book
is actually physical,
not digital.
Yeah and hidden
in one of these lockers.
Ready to look for a needle
in a very large haystack?
Oh, my God.
Okay, look, um,
I had plans with Emma,
so let me call her and cancel.
And then we'll roll
our sleeves up and get going.
Stop. Whoa.
Go spend time
with your girlfriend.
Yeah. We'll tag you
back in tomorrow.
We got this.
Okay.
Thanks.
- I'm fine, Pop.
- Shouldn't have improvised.
Nothing on the Charger.
But now I got some ideas
for my next car lease.
- This is a sexy car.
- You know what?
Let's call it.
You should go home,
and I don't wanna be late.
Hot date with Charlie?
Guess he got over the polygraph.
Yeah, he took it surprisingly
well, all things considered.
Border patrol
found that license plate
you were looking for
abandoned outside El Paso.
You think our mystery man
ditched the plates
before crossing the border?
Yeah, you've been saying
that the revenue stream
would uncover
the Maguires' next move.
And this confirms our intel
that Connor is making in-runs
with the cartels.
We'll need to relocate
some personnel.
- Relocate?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna make a recommendation
that you oversee the operation.
I hear great things
about our Juárez station.
Diplomatic cover,
an international operation,
real action.
I'm a honeypot away from
finishing my bucket list.
Em, this is huge.
Yeah.
Huge.
♪ I think I see it... ♪
I'm surprised you're here.
I thought your band had a gig.
Oh, yeah the, uh,
the tour bus broke down,
so I'm here for another night.
Lucky for you.
Lucky for me?
I hope I'm not interrupting.
♪ Waitin' for me... ♪
I know you have
your botany symposium tomorrow.
It's a... growing problem.
Nice.
♪ Right out where
the sun will set... ♪
You're here.
♪ Maybe I'm dreamin' ♪
I'm here.
♪ A dream
when I'm fine with ♪
♪ I'll rage on... ♪
I'm glad we're doing this.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, I think we both needed it.
♪ Maybe I love how I feel
in the wind and the breeze ♪
♪ So light ♪
♪ I'm light... ♪
You ever think about
where we'd be
if we hadn't sat at that bar
at that moment?
Ha. I try not to
think about it.
♪ Li-i-i-ight ♪
♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♪ Close to you? ♪
♪ Feel it, feel it... ♪
Come to Mexico with me.
Great.
I'll gas up the private jet,
you bring the champagne.
No, Charlie, I'm serious.
♪ Feel it, feel it... ♪
Why Mexico?
Well, I... can't say exactly.
♪ Maybe I love the way
I can fall on my feet... ♪
Oh, you... you're working.
♪ Maybe I love
how I feel... ♪
Got ya.
♪ I'm the breeze,
so light... ♪
Look, I...
Honestly, if my boss
had asked me two months ago,
I wouldn't have hesitated.
And I know it's impulsive,
which is so not me,
but the thing is...
I already can't sleep
when you're not next to me.
I love you.
Oh, God.
It's not what you think.
You don't need to explain.
- It's fine. Totally fine.
- It's...
- No, it's so fine.
- No, no, no, no.
I-it's not fine. Emma...
- I'm gonna go.
- Please don't go.
- Please, Emma, just stay.
- No.
I'm not gonna stay.
Bye, Charlie.
- Hey.
Aren't you, uh, supposed to be
waking up in silk sheets
right about now?
No, hotel switched
to pima cotton.
Wasn't digging the thread count.
Mm-hmm.
Night ended early.
- You getting a fresh pot?
- Yeah, sure.
Hey, so where're we at
with Baylor's black book?
- What'd I miss?
- Uh, Pop and I got through
about half the list last night.
There's still 214 buildings to
go with 32 or more lockers.
You wanna split it up?
I'll take Northeast DC.
You take Northwest.
First, how 'bout you tell me
why you been lying to me.
Yeah, okay.
You've been weird.
I've been patient.
Hey, Bird, we're all going
through a lot right now.
Oh, stop it.
You're my brother.
What's going on?
Hmm. Emma.
I don't think
it's gonna work out.
Why? What happened?
We're just too different.
She don't know about
any of this.
I don't like hiding it from her.
Yeah.
Gotta let it go though.
Whatever we had,
it's in the past.
Let the past stay the past.
What's that?
I think I know where to find
Baylor's black book.
It's my decision to make.
Because I'm the candidate,
not my father.
We can discuss this later.
I heard you come home
last night.
What happened to
your stay-cation?
I think we're done.
Why? What happened?
I said the I word.
And Charlie didn't say it back.
It just... sorta came out,
but I...
Still thought he would...
I mean, I literally
read people for a living.
How could I have been so off?
I was so sure it was real.
I finally let someone in.
I am really sorry, Em.
Yeah.
Me too.
Thornton's campus.
Baylor spent years there
undercover as a professor.
Minutes away from his fat cat
clients on Capitol Hill.
He'd know the place
inside and out.
So remember Baylor's key
had RM printed on it.
Guess which library
has 50 thesis lockers
that use that same key?
Reim Memorial.
Oh, it looks like
your Hail Mary paid off, Bird.
I'll dust off Professor Bloom
so I can keep guard.
I think I still got that
tweed jacket
- laying around here somewhere.
- I miss that guy.
- He still teaching astronomy?
- Russian history.
Reading a lot of Trotsky lately.
He's a fascinating man.
Okay, so while
Professor Pinko's keeping
an eye on the door,
all we gotta do
is pick Baylor's lock,
copy the black book,
and then put it back before
he ever knew we were there.
Oh, is that all?
♪ And you got it ♪
♪ Lady, you got it ♪
♪ Got it, yeah ♪
♪ Show me ♪
That can't be it.
Look.
You gotta be kidding me.
It's just a box of microfiche?
I mean,
we knew he was old-school,
but this is ancient.
He must shrink it down
to make it easier to hide.
So how're we gonna copy it?
Uh... there was a scanner
that we passed.
It'll let me dump it
onto a flash drive.
- It's gonna take a while.
- All right.
Then let's get goin'.
Oh, no, no.
But the thing about Lenin
is that he was always
jealous of Trotsky,
because Trotsky
had the gift of gab.
I'm tellin' ya, if the
Astrodome had been around...
Trotsky would've packed it.
He had presence.
Yeah, uh, excuse me a minute.
Baylor's incoming.
Got about 20 seconds.
I'll distract him.
You keep going.
Hey, Charlie, he's armed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's why I gotta do this.
That should give you time.
Hey, Bird, Dad, you guys clear?
Hey, I'm in.
I'm in the van.
Okay. I'll meet you
outside then.
Hey, pal.
Hello again.
I believe you came
to take something of mine,
so I thought
I'd take something of yours.
You know, there's an easier way
to register for my class.
Let him go.
Who? Your father here?
I thought so.
I take it that was your sister
in my car as well.
Family of criminals.
Holidays must be a delight.
Hey, Pop, Charlie, you keep
him talking, all right?
I'm gonna find us
something we can use.
You calling us criminals?
People pay you
to fix their problems,
an then you steal their secrets
for blackmail?
Cost of doing business;
if my clients really wanted to
protect themselves,
they'd have no secrets.
Everybody's
hiding something, pal.
Except you.
No, someone spilled your secret.
How's it feel to be disavowed
by your country?
Having my cover blown
left me with nothing to hide.
Unlike you, I have nothing
that makes me vulnerable.
What's your play here?
Steal my collateral
to make a buck?
I'd like to steal
that gun of yours
and stick it up your...
Oh!
You okay?
Yeah.
It's all there.
Even so...
I can't let you out of here
knowing what you know.
Hey, Charlie,
I think I got something.
Those books in Baylor's locker
were written by the wife
of the dean who blew his cover.
- She's his secret.
- Katherine Moss.
She's the reason
you got burned, right?
You two were having an affair,
and when her husband found out,
he was the one who exposed you.
But you're still carrying
a torch for her.
It's romantic, really.
You think I care about her?
The past is the past.
Then why are you keeping
the books she gave you
in your locker?
Okay, Charlie, I found her.
She lives at 39...
44 Brandywine.
That's where she lives
with her husband, the dean.
- Right?
- Don't you dare go near her.
As long as you stay clear of
us, she's gonna be fine.
But the second I sniff you
anywhere nearby...
I'm gonna let all
your enemies know
where to find her.
Deal?
Deal.
Good morning, everyone.
I wanted to introduce you
to your new
Director of Social Media,
Jennifer West.
- Hey.
- Hey, Jen.
I have complete faith in Jen,
and I know you all will too.
We need to stop making assumptions
and see each other
for who we really are.
That goes double for voters.
Together, we can bring
real change to Washington.
And let's get to work.
Nice digs.
I know, right?
I acquired it from
some new business partners.
You see, Charlie?
Cooperation has its benefits.
Yeah.
Got you what you needed.
So much power
in the palm of my hand.
This should take off, what,
2 million off your debt,
let's say?
Debt, right.
That's between you and Connor.
You're lucky
I'm feeling generous,
considering
the information on here
solves your problems
as much as mine.
- How would it do that?
- Well,
the feds spotted you
handing stolen cash
to a drug dealer you brought
stateside, so... yes.
You might need
some dirty politicians.
You got a particular
scumbag in mind,
or did you just nearly get
my family and I killed
for a fishing expedition?
All you need to know
is the blackmail on here
will get the feds off
both of our trails for good.
I took care of that drop car.
All right?
They not on to us anymore.
I don't think you understand
who we're up against.
There's this little
CIA spook... she's smart.
Tenacious.
A real caped crusader.
But lucky for us, her family
isn't quite so principled.
Politicians, am I right?
I bet a threat to her family
will put a nice little dent
in her can-do spirit.
Emma.
What are you doing here?
We need to talk.
Nothing more to say.
Hey, Daphne Finch
is coming for you.
How do you know that name?
Because I'm working for her.
Oh, my God.
It's you... the guy in the mask.
Look, she's got dirt
on your family,
and she intends to use it
against you, Emma.
Why are you telling me this?